Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not Annotated
      - R
        - Rasco - Thin line; Gunz still hot (remix), 2001; SR-23719; Rasco (Box 407)
          Copasetik Recordings
        - Rashad - Tell 'em what they wanna hear, 2006; SR-23720; Rashad (Box 407)
          Catalog # PR 302221; A-side Matrix # STA 94283 A-1 REI SIDE 1
        - Rasheeda - Georgia peach, 2005; SR-23721; Rasheeda (Box 407)
          Catalog # JDAB-71660-1; A-side Matrix # JDAB-71660-1A
          Jive
        - Rashid & The Boot Camp - Sexy but deadly; Bring the funk, 1994; SR-23722; Rashid & The Boot Camp (Box 407)
          Catalog # TG137; A-side Matrix # TG-137-A
          Simply Raw Records
          Far Rockaway, New York
        - Rashid, Karen - It’s your life (think twice), 1990; SR-23723; Rashid, Karen (Box 407)
          Catalog # LUV-6301; A-side Matrix # LUV-6301-A
          Love Understanding Vibrations
          Clinton, Maryland
        - Rashien - In '88, 1988; SR-23724; Rashien (Box 407)
          Catalog # PAL-7189-DJ; A-side Matrix # PAL-7189-A
          Rooftop Records
        - Raulin - Soca salsa, 1989; SR-23725; Raulin (Box 407)
          Catalog # K-60036; A-side Matrix # 60036-A
          Kubaney
        - Raulin - Soca salsa, 1989; SR-23726; Raulin (Box 407)
        - Rava, Enrico - Enrico Rava Quartet, 1979; SR-23727; Rava, Enrico; Enrico Rava Quartet (Box 407)
          Catalog # ECM-1-1122; A-side Matrix # 34092 ECM-1-1122 A
          ECM Records
          Munich, Germany
        - Raven, Marcia - Catch me (I'm falling in love), 1983; SR-23728; Raven, Marcia (Box 407)
          Catalog # PRO-7034-DJ; A-side Matrix # PRO-7034A-1
        - Raven-Symoné - That's what little girls are made of, 1993; SR-23729; Raven-Symoné (Box 407)
          Catalog # MCA8P-2635; A-side Matrix # MCA-11672-2
          MCA Records
        - Raven-Symoné - That's what little girls are made of, 1993; SR-23730; Raven-Symoné (Box 407)
        - Raven-Symoné - That's what little girls are made of, 1993; SR-23731; Raven-Symoné (Box 407)
          Catalog # MCA 12-54654; A-side Matrix # MCA-11675-HF2
        - Ravi Harris & The Prophets - Funky sitar man, 1997; SR-23732; Ravi Harris & The Prophets (Box 407)
          Catalog # BBELP002; A-side Matrix # BBE LP 002 A1 DAMONT
          BBE
          Hastings, United Kingdom
        - Raw - Stand by your man, 1994; SR-23733; Raw (Box 407)
          Catalog # PRO-A-7126; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-7126 SR-1
          Reprise Records
        - Raw Beats - Raw beats #40, 1999; SR-23734; Raw Beats (Box 407)
          Catalog # RB-40; A-side Matrix # RB-40 A
          Raw Beats
          Redwood City, California
        - Raw Beats - Raw beats #68, 2002; SR-23735; Raw Beats (Box 407)
          Catalog # RB-68; A-side Matrix # RB-68 A S-50214
        - Raw Beats - Raw beats #61, 2001; SR-23736; Raw Beats (Box 407)
          Catalog # RB-61; A-side Matrix # RB-61 A1 S-48333
        - Raw Beats - Raw beats #35, 1998; SR-23737; Raw Beats (Box 407)
          Catalog # RB-35; A-side Matrix # RB-35 A S-38219
        - Raw Beats - Raw beats #43, 1999; SR-23738; Raw Beats (Box 407)
          Catalog # RB-43; A-side Matrix # RB-43 A S-42129
        - Raw Beats - Raw beats #29, 1997; SR-23739; Raw Beats (Box 407)
          Catalog # RB-29; A-side Matrix # RB 29 A1 S-35552
        - Raw Beats - Raw beats #11, 1994; SR-23740; Raw Beats (Box 407)
          Catalog # RB-11; A-side Matrix # RB-11 A2 L-42502
        - Raw Beats - Raw beats #41, 1999; SR-23741; Raw Beats (Box 408)
          Catalog # RB-41; A-side Matrix # RB-41 A1
        - Raw Beats - Raw beats 50 hip hop classic edition, 2000; SR-23742; Raw Beats (Box 408)
          Catalog # RB-50; A-side Matrix # RB-50 A S-45159
        - Raw Beats - Raw beats #64, 2002; SR-23743; Raw Beats (Box 408)
          Catalog # RB-64; A-side Matrix # RB-64 A1 S-48756
        - Raw Beats - Raw beats #59, 2001; SR-23744; Raw Beats (Box 408)
          Catalog # RB-59; A-side Matrix # RB-59 A1 S-47721
        - Raw Breed - I want in; Mouth of madness pt. 2, 1997; SR-23745; Raw Breed (Box 408)
          Catalog # PRO-A-8780; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-8780-A-SR1
          Warner Bros. Records
        - Raw Breed - Rabbit stew, 1993; SR-23746; Raw Breed (Box 408)
          Catalog # 12305-1; A-side Matrix # 12305-1-A DMM LSP1-1
          Continuum Records
          Cranford, New Jersey
        - Raw Core - This house is booming, 1990; SR-23747; Raw Core (Box 408)
          Catalog # V-72274; A-side Matrix # V-1-72274-Z1-DMM SP1-1
          Orpheus Records
        - Raw Division - Language of the drumz, 1995; SR-23748; Raw Division (Box 408)
          Catalog # SP71; A-side Matrix # SP-71A
          Jihad Records
        - Raw Division - Language of the drumz, 1995; SR-23749; Raw Division (Box 408)
        - Raw G - Busykickinrhymes2therythem, 1993; SR-23750; Raw G (Box 408)
          Catalog # OT-5003-S; A-side Matrix # OT-5003-A
          O-Town Records
          Orlando, Florida
        - Raw Image - Break down (Disc one), 1998; SR-23751; Raw Image (Box 408)
          In same jacket as # SR-23752. Double album.
          Catalog # PA 1026; A-side Matrix # PA-1026-A
          Future Records & Tapes
          Landover, Maryland
        - Raw Image - Break down (Disc two), 1998; SR-23752; Raw Image (Box 408)
          In same jacket as # SR-23751. Double album.
          Catalog # PA 1026; A-side Matrix # PA-1026-C
        - Raw Junkies - Turn up the radio, 2000; SR-23753; Raw Junkies (Box 408)
          Catalog # GH 7001; A-side Matrix # GH-7001-A PA-11-99
          Ghetto House
        - Raw Junkies - Turn up the radio, 2000; SR-23754; Raw Junkies (Box 408)
        - Raw Produce - Cycles; Make a mark, 1995; SR-23755; Raw Produce (Box 408)
          Catalog # RP 5195; A-side Matrix # CELERY SIDE RP-5195
          Insomnia Records
          Boston, Massachusetts
        - Raw Sex - Stop the war; Give sheep a chance, 1982; SR-23756; Raw Sex (Box 408)
          Catalog # MLPS 7797; A-side Matrix # MLPS-7797-A
        - Raw Sex - Stop the war; Give sheep a chance, 1982; SR-23757; Raw Sex (Box 408)
          In same jacket as # SR-23758. Different discs.
        - Raw Sex - Stop the war; Give sheep a chance, 1982; SR-23758; Raw Sex; Pure Energy (Box 408)
          In same jacket as # SR-23757. Different discs.
          Catalog # 12WIP 6797; A-side Matrix # 12WIP 6797 A-1U-1-1-
          Island Records
        - Raw Stilo - Cutie, 1995; SR-23759; Raw Stilo (Box 408)
          Catalog # 31458 1213 1; A-side Matrix # 31458-1213-1A SPI 1-1
        - Raw Stilo - Cutie, 1995; SR-23760; Raw Stilo (Box 408)
          Catalog # DVPRO00155; A-side Matrix # DVPRO 00155 A -SPI
          DV8 Records
        - Rawdog - Arrest the president; Spies in the coffin; The snake charmer, 2003; SR-23761; Rawdog (Box 408)
          Catalog # LOW 25; A-side Matrix # LOW25-A-
          Low Life Records
        - Rawlins, Wandra - Love attack, 1983; SR-23762; Rawlins, Wandra (Box 408)
          Catalog # JAM 3010; A-side Matrix # JAM 3010 A
          Jamtu Records
          Cherry Hill, New Jersey
        - Rawls, Lou - The best of Lou Rawls, 1986; SR-23763; Rawls, Lou (Box 408)
          Catalog # SN-16096; A-side Matrix # SN-1-16096 H-1
          Capitol Records
        - Rawls, Lou - Live (Disc one), 1978; SR-23764; Rawls, Lou (Box 408)
          In same jacket as # SR-23765. Double album.
          Catalog # PZ2 35517; A-side Matrix # AL-35518-1A-2HZ:
          Philadelphia International Records
          Philadelphia, Pennsylvania
        - Rawls, Lou - Live (Disc two), 1978; SR-23765; Rawls, Lou (Box 408)
          In same jacket as # SR-23764. Double album.
          Catalog # PZ2 35517; A-side Matrix # AL-35519-1A-2HZ
        - Rawls, Lou - Soulin', 1966; SR-23766; Rawls, Lou (Box 408)
          Catalog # T-2566; A-side Matrix # T-1-2566-F-3
        - Rawls, Lou - Live at the Century Plaza, 1973; SR-23767; Rawls, Lou (Box 408)
          Catalog # SE 4895; A-side Matrix # SE 4895 MGS 3106-RE-1
          MGM Records
        - Rawls, Lou - Let me be good to you, 1979; SR-23768; Rawls, Lou (Box 408)
          Catalog # 2Z8 3686; A-side Matrix # P.I.R. AB-2Z8-3686-3 "YOU'LL NEVER FORGET OUR TUNES"
        - Rawls, Lou - Carryin' on!, 1966; SR-23769; Rawls, Lou (Box 408)
          Catalog # T-2632; A-side Matrix # T1-2632-P1
        - Ray, Billy - In and out, 1995; SR-23770; Ray, Billy (Box 408)
          Catalog # BE-1; A-side Matrix # BE-1-A
          56 Blitz Entertainment
          New York
        - Ray, Don - The garden of love, 1978; SR-23771; Ray, Don (Box 408)
          Catalog # PD-1-6150; A-side Matrix # PD-1-6150-AS-K1
          Polydor
        - Ray, Don - Got to have loving, 1978; SR-23772; Ray, Don (Box 408)
          Catalog # PRO 048; A-side Matrix # PRO-048-78-NP-3603-S-GD1
        - Ray, Fay - Contact you, 1982; SR-23773; Ray, Fay (Box 408)
          Catalog # E1-60098; A-side Matrix # E1-60098A-1 SH-SP
        - Ray, Goodman & Brown - Where did you get that body baby?, 1988; SR-23774; Ray, Goodman & Brown (Box 408)
          Catalog # V-56115; A-side Matrix # V-1-56115 -22-DMM 1-1
          EMI Manhattan Records
        - Ray J - Quit actin', 2005; SR-23775; Ray J (Box 408)
          Catalog # SURDJ-85685-1; A-side Matrix # SURDJ-85685-1 A
          Sanctuary Records
          Chicago, Illinois
        - Ray J - Let it go remix, 1996; SR-23776; Ray J (Box 408)
          Catalog # ED-6021; A-side Matrix # ST-ED- 6021-63979-A-1
          EastWest Records America
        - Ray J - Let it go, 1996; SR-23777; Ray J (Box 408)
          Catalog # ED-5889; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-5889-A-1
        - Ray J - Wait a minute, 2001; SR-23778; Ray J; Lil' Kim (Box 408)
          Catalog # PR 300452; A-side Matrix # ST-PR 90095-90096-1
        - Ray King Soul Band - Live at the Playboy Club, 1968; SR-23779; Ray King Soul Band (Box 408)
          Catalog # 8-63394; A-side Matrix # 8-63394 A
          Direction
          São Paulo, Brazil
        - Ray Luv - Who can be trusted?, 1992; SR-23780; Ray Luv (Box 408)
          Catalog # SBLP 2027; A-side Matrix # SBLP-2027 A1 S-26503
          Strictly Business Records
          Vallejo, California
        - Ray Luv - Definition of ah hustla; Ride with the luvva man, 1995; SR-23781; Ray Luv (Box 408)
          Catalog # PR 6492; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-79772-79773-79775-1
        - Ray Luv - In the game, 1995; SR-23782; Ray Luv (Box 408)
          Catalog # PR 6193; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-76717-76718-76719-1
        - Ray Luv - In the game, 1995; SR-23783; Ray Luv (Box 408)
        - Rayde, Ayre - Sock it to me, 1986; SR-23784; Rayde, Ayre (Box 408)
          Catalog # CR 01; A-side Matrix # CR-01-A
          Full House Records
          Oakton, Virginia
        - Raye, Mona - I've been watching you, 1984; SR-23785; Raye, Mona (Box 408)
          Catalog # WES DJ 2176; A-side Matrix # WES-22176A-70630
          West End Records
        - Rayer - Carjack les cardiaks, 1998; SR-23786; Rayer (Box 408)
          Catalog # RAY.012; A-side Matrix # RAY 012-A- (Rayer)
          9mm Recordz
          Schaerbeek, Belgium
        - Raymun - Do you feel like I feel, 1983; SR-23787; Raymun (Box 408)
          Catalog # CW 80911; A-side Matrix # CW-80911-A
          Clockwork Records
        - Rayvon - 2-way, 2001; SR-23788; Rayvon (Box 408)
          Catalog # 088 155 891-1; A-side Matrix # 088-155-891-1A
        - Raz - Do it kinda funky; Everybody move, 2000; SR-23789; Raz (Box 408)
          Catalog # FNK-001; A-side Matrix # FNK-001 A
          Funktopia Records
        - Raze - A dynamite EP, 1989; SR-23790; Raze; Project (Box 408)
          In same jacket as # SR-23791. 2 copies.
          Catalog # M 870; A-side Matrix # M-870-A
          Giant
        - Raze - A dynamite EP, 1989; SR-23791; Raze; Project (Box 408)
          In same jacket as # SR-23790. 2 copies.
        - Raze - Jump in your dance; Jack the groove, 1986; SR-23792; Raze (Box 408)
          Catalog # GR-852; A-side Matrix # GR-852-A
          Grove St.
          Orange, New Jersey
        - Raze - Grove Street DJ tool #3, 1994; SR-23793; Raze; Mistawrek (Box 408)
          Catalog # GSR-21218; A-side Matrix # GSR-21218-A EUROPADISK DMM NY USA 47996 DON GROSSINGER
        - Razed High - Invisible, 2001; SR-23794; Razed High (Box 408)
          Catalog # IUR9004-1; A-side Matrix # IUR-9004-1A S-48044 BLIND BY CHOICE
          Insiduous Urban Records
        - RBL Posse - An eye for an eye (Disc one), 1997; SR-23795; RBL Posse (Box 409)
          In same jacket as # SR-23796. Double album.
          Catalog # 92771-1; A-side Matrix # ST-BB-971235B
        - RBL Posse - An eye for an eye (Disc two), 1997; SR-23796; RBL Posse (Box 409)
          In same jacket as # SR-23795. Double album.
          Catalog # 92771-1; A-side Matrix # ST-BB-971237B
        - RBL Posse - Bounce to this RMX, 1995; SR-23797; RBL Posse (Box 409)
          Catalog # INA8711-1; A-side Matrix # S-31087
          In-A-Minute Records
          Oakland, California
        - RBL Posse - Bounce to this, 1994; SR-23798; RBL Posse (Box 409)
          Catalog # INA8701; A-side Matrix # INA8701 S-30177REI SIDE A
        - R.B.M - Yo shorty (the remixes), 1995; SR-23799; R.B.M (Box 409)
          Catalog # SR 12391; A-side Matrix # SR-12391-A EUROPADISK DMM NY USA 12695
          Strictly Rhythm
          Uniondale, New York
        - RBX - Rough is the texture; A.W.O.L., 1995; SR-23800; RBX (Box 409)
          Catalog # 0-43599; A-side Matrix # 0-43599-A-SRI
          Premeditated Records
        - RBX - The RBX files (Disc one), 1995; SR-23801; RBX (Box 409)
          In same jacket as # SR-23802. Double album.
          Catalog # PRO-A-7881; A-side Matrix # PRO A 7881 A SRI
        - RBX - The RBX files (Disc two), 1995; SR-23802; RBX (Box 409)
          In same jacket as # SR-23801. Double album.
          Catalog # PRO-A-7881; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-7881-C-SRI
        - RBX - Rough is the texture; Our time is now, 1995; SR-23803; RBX (Box 409)
          Catalog # PRO-A-7819; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-7819-A-SR2
          Premeditated
        - RBX - Rough is the texture; Our time is now, 1995; SR-29723; RBX (Box 409)
        - Re-Flex - The politics of dancing, 1983; SR-23804; Re-Flex (Box 409)
          Catalog # 8574; A-side Matrix # 8574-X600682-C F-1
        - Re-Flex - The politics of dancing, 1983; SR-23805; Re-Flex (Box 409)
        - Rea, Kova - Annabelle, 1989; SR-23806; Rea, Kova (Box 409)
          Catalog # 874 087-1; A-side Matrix # MPO I 874 087-1 A GOOD LUCK
          Philips
          France
        - Reachout - Everything u knew, 1998; SR-23807; Reachout (Box 409)
          Catalog # OE 001; A-side Matrix # OI-1-A "THANKS TO JO THE SALSAHNT"
          Oh-Eye Records
          Edinburgh, United Kingdom
        - Reaction - My downtown lady; Hunter, 1985; SR-23808; Reaction (Box 409)
          Catalog # SRU-72310; A-side Matrix # SRU-72310
          Strawberry Records Unltd.
          Mount Vernon, New York
        - Ready For The World - Mary goes 'round (extended version), 1987; SR-23809; Ready For The World (Box 409)
          Catalog # MCA-23723; A-side Matrix # MCA-6610-FDS-1
        - Ready For The World - Mary goes 'round, 1986; SR-23810; Ready For The World (Box 409)
          Catalog # L33-17256; A-side Matrix # MCA-6468-FDS-2
        - Ready For The World - Here I am (extended version) (12" version), 1987; SR-23811; Ready For The World (Box 409)
          Catalog # MCA-23788; A-side Matrix # MCA7175 FDS-1
        - Ready For The World - Straight down to business, 1991; SR-23812; Ready For The World (Box 409)
          Catalog # MCA12 54122; A-side Matrix # MCA-10798 FDS-2
        - Ready For The World - Love you down, 1986; SR-23813; Ready For The World (Box 409)
          Catalog # L33-17208; A-side Matrix # MCA-6217-FDS-2
        - Ready For The World - Ceramic girl, 1986; SR-23814; Ready For The World (Box 409)
          Catalog # MCA-23618; A-side Matrix # MCA 5316 FDS-1FILTILRE DISC
        - Ready For The World - My girly, 1988; SR-23815; Ready For The World (Box 409)
          Catalog # L33-17647; A-side Matrix # MCA8269 FDS-1
        - Ready For The World - Long time coming (12" version), 1987; SR-23816; Ready For The World (Box 409)
          Catalog # MCA-23758; A-side Matrix # MCA-6886-FDS-1
        - Ready For The World - Tonight, 1984; SR-23817; Ready For The World (Box 409)
          Catalog # MCA-23527; A-side Matrix # MCA-4263-FDS-1
        - Ready For The World - Slide over, 1985; SR-23818; Ready For The World (Box 409)
          Catalog # L33-17061; A-side Matrix # MCA-4967-FDS-1
        - Ready For The World - Digital display, 1985; SR-23819; Ready For The World (Box 409)
          Catalog # L33-17067; A-side Matrix # MCA-4935-FDS-1
        - Ready For The World - My girly, 1988; SR-23820; Ready For The World (Box 409)
          In same jacket as # SR-23821. 2 copies.
        - Ready For The World - My girly, 1988; SR-23821; Ready For The World (Box 409)
          In same jacket as # SR-23820. 2 copies.
        - Ready For The World - Love you down, 1986; SR-23822; Ready For The World (Box 409)
        - Ready For The World - Love you down, 1986; SR-23823; Ready For The World (Box 409)
          In same jacket as # SR-23824. Different discs.
          Catalog # L33-17197; A-side Matrix # MCA 6154 FDS-1 FUTURE DISC
        - Ready For The World - Love you down, 1986; SR-23824; Ready For The World (Box 409)
          In same jacket as # SR-23823. Different discs.
          Catalog # MCA-23680; A-side Matrix # MCA 6154 FDS-1 FUTURE DISC
        - Ready For The World - Ruff 'n' ready, 1988; SR-23825; Ready For The World (Box 409)
          Catalog # MCA-42198; A-side Matrix # MCA-7858-FDS-6 Future Disc
        - Ready Ta Roll - Drug game; Taste the flavor, 1994; SR-23826; Ready Ta Roll (Box 409)
          Catalog # PC-0953; A-side Matrix # PC-0953-A
          Chanpen Records
          Jersey City, New Jersey
        - Ready Ta Roll - Drug game; Taste the flavor, 1994; SR-23827; Ready Ta Roll (Box 409)
        - Real Fish - ジャンクビート東京, 1987; SR-23828; Real Fish (Box 409)
          Catalog # VIH-12004; A-side Matrix # VIH-12004A 111+A
          Invitation
        - The Two - The real Grandmaster, 1986; SR-23829; The Two (Box 409)
          In same jacket as # SR-23830. 2 copies.
          Catalog # PRO-7100; A-side Matrix # PRO-7100-A
        - The Two - The real Grandmaster, 1986; SR-23830; The Two (Box 409)
          In same jacket as # SR-23829. 2 copies.
        - Real Raw! - Drop them draws, 1988; SR-23831; Real Raw! (Box 409)
          Catalog # FL-2; A-side Matrix # A WORLD PREMIERE FL2
          World Premiere Records
          Hialeah, Florida
        - Real Roxanne - Roxanne's on a roll, 1989; SR-23832; Real Roxanne (Box 409)
          In same jacket as # SR-23833. 2 copies.
          Catalog # FMS 62334; A-side Matrix # FMS 62334 A F/W
        - Real Roxanne - Roxanne's on a roll, 1989; SR-23833; Real Roxanne (Box 409)
          In same jacket as # SR-23832. 2 copies.
        - Real Roxanne - Respect, 1988; SR-23834; Real Roxanne (Box 409)
          Catalog # FMS 62318; A-side Matrix # FMS-62318-A
        - Real Roxanne - Respect, 1988; SR-23835; Real Roxanne (Box 409)
        - Real Roxanne - The Real Roxanne, 1988; SR-23836; Real Roxanne (Box 409)
          Catalog # 839 665-1; A-side Matrix # 8396651 A-1U-1-1
          Urban
        - Real Roxanne - Bang zoom! (Let's go-go); Howie's teed off, 1986; SR-23837; Real Roxanne; Hitman Howie Tee (Box 409)
          Catalog # FMS 62269; A-side Matrix # FMS-62269-A
        - Real Roxanne - Romeo, 1985; SR-23838; Real Roxanne; Hitman Howie Tee (Box 409)
          Catalog # FMS 62260; A-side Matrix # FMS 62260 A
        - Real Roxanne - Romeo, 1985; SR-23839; Real Roxanne; Hitman Howie Tee (Box 409)
        - Real Street - Dedicated, 1995; SR-23840; Real Street (Box 409)
          Catalog # REAL; A-side Matrix # REAL-A
          Real Street Records
          Nyack, New York
        - Real Thing - Can you feel the force?, 1978; SR-23841; Real Thing (Box 409)
          Catalog # AS 646; A-side Matrix # XSS-165492-2E
        - Real to Reel - Can you treat me like she does?, 1983; SR-23842; Real to Reel (Box 409)
          Catalog # ADP 1 9081; A-side Matrix # AD1-9081-SA-PROMO F 1
          Arista
        - Reality - One big party, 1998; SR-23843; Reality (Box 409)
          Catalog # MHZ59; A-side Matrix # MHZ-59-A
          35MHZ Records
        - Reality Enterprises - Stick & move, 1986; SR-23844; Reality Enterprises (Box 409)
          Catalog # CRIM 00005; A-side Matrix # CRIM 00005 A
          Criminal Records
        - Reaves, Paulette - Do it again, 1981; SR-23845; Reaves, Paulette (Box 409)
          In same jacket as # SR-23846. 2 copies. Annotated.
          Catalog # DD 6001; A-side Matrix # DD-6001-A
          Dash
        - Reaves, Paulette - Do it again, 1981; SR-23846; Reaves, Paulette (Box 409)
          In same jacket as # SR-23845. 2 copies.
        - [Unknown] - Rebel Beats 2, 1988; SR-23847 (Box 409)
          Unknown artist
          Catalog # PTRB 002; A-side Matrix # PT-R-B-002-A
          Pan Trax
        - Rebel MC - Black meaning good, 1991; SR-23848; Rebel MC (Box 409)
          Catalog # WANTX 47; A-side Matrix # WANTX-47-A
          Desire Records
        - Rebel MC - Rebel music, 1990; SR-23849; Rebel MC; De La Soul (Box 410)
          Catalog # PRO 855-1; A-side Matrix # PRO-855-1 A-SP
        - Rebel MC - Culture; Comin' on strong, 1990; SR-23850; Rebel MC (Box 410)
          A note addresses to Lindsey fron Desire records inside
          Catalog # WANTX 38 P; A-side Matrix # WANTX38A4
        - Rebel, Tony - My way or the highway; The voice & the pen, 1993; SR-23851; Rebel, Tony (Box 410)
          Catalog # OAS 6240; A-side Matrix # XSS-6240-A-1A
          Chaos Records
        - Rebels - Banana, 1989; SR-23852; Rebels (Box 410)
          Catalog # K-20018; A-side Matrix # 20018-A
        - Rebels - Banana (bobine), 1989; SR-23853; Rebels (Box 410)
          Catalog # K-60033; A-side Matrix # 60033
        - Rebels - Banana (bobine), 1989; SR-23854; Rebels (Box 410)
        - Rebels - You can make it, 1984; SR-23855; Rebels (Box 410)
          Catalog # CEL 172; A-side Matrix # B- CEL 172 A
          Celluloid
        - Rebels - You can make it, 1984; SR-23856; Rebels (Box 410)
          In same jacket as # SR-23857. 2 copies.
        - Rebels - You can make it, 1984; SR-23857; Rebels (Box 410)
          In same jacket as # SR-23856. 2 copies.
        - Rebirth - Evil vibrations (Saturday mix), 2007; SR-23858; Rebirth (Box 410)
          Catalog # OSSD 003; A-side Matrix # OSSd-003-A
          Oriental Source Sound & Distribution
        - Rebels - Soca party combination, 1989; SR-23859; Rebels (Box 410)
          Catalog # GS 2302; A-side Matrix # GS-2302-A STRANGE RECORD WORLD-VP-CS
          Straker's Records
        - Red Black & Green - Serious as cancer; Feel the groove, 1989; SR-23860; Red Black & Green (Box 410)
          In same jacket as # SR-23861. 2 copies.
          Catalog # RF-001; A-side Matrix # RF 001 A1 DEDICATED TO S.T.V. S-21734
          Rapid Fire Recordings
          Santa Cruz, California
        - Red Black & Green - Serious as cancer; Feel the groove, 1989; SR-23861; Red Black & Green (Box 410)
          In same jacket as # SR-23860. 2 copies.
        - Red Café - May I; The virus, 2003; SR-23862; Red Café (Box 410)
          Catalog # RC003A; A-side Matrix # RC 003 A
          Brookland Records
        - Red China - Property, 1995; SR-23863; Red China (Box 410)
          Catalog # MM 104; A-side Matrix # MM-104-A PROPERTY
          Hardcore Respek
          Freeport, Long Island, New York